petinsurance.com 2006-12-06

# Veterinary Pet Insurance - Insurance for Dogs, Cats, Puppies, Kittens, Avians, Exotics

Privacy Statement

We comply with the GLB privacy act as governed by federal law. For your convenience we have provided our privacy policy in conjunction with our national underwriter National Casualty Company and their property/casualty division Scottsdale Insurance Company.

We value you as a customer and respect your right to privacy. We know that you purchase our products and services because you trust that we will stand behind our promises. We pledge our commitment to treat your information responsibly. We created this privacy policy to show you that we are working hard to protect your privacy.

How do we protect the confidentiality and security of your information? We use physical and technical safeguards to protect your information. We restrict access to your information to those who need it to perform their jobs. Third-party business partners are bound by law to use the information only for our purposes. They may not disclose it or use it in any other way. We comply with all data security laws.

What personal information do we collect about you? We collect personal information about you from different sources. 

  * We collect information you send us on applications and forms. 
  * We collect information from your transactions with us, our sister companies, or others. 
  * Based on the product or services requested, we may collect information from a consumer reporting agency or a medical provider. 

What types of information do we disclose and to whom? We do not sell your information to anyone. We may disclose this information to a business that carries out services and marketing for us. We may disclose your information as required or permitted by law. We may disclose your information for a legal or regulatory purpose. These include the following types of information: 

  * Information we receive from you on applications or other forms. This may include your name, address, beneficiaries, Social Security number, and family member information. This may also include assets, income, and the property address and value. 
  * This may include information from your transactions with our sister companies, or us. It may include your account balance, policy coverage, and payment history. It may also include premium paid, preferences, shares you purchase, claims, and purchase method. 
  * This may include information we receive from a consumer-reporting agency or other reporting agencies. It may include, your credit report, motor vehicle and driver data. It may also include medical and employment data, loss history reports, and other driver data. These depend on the products you select. 
  * We may disclose information to companies that perform marketing services on our behalf. As permitted by law, we may disclose some information to other financial institutions with which we have joint marketing agreements. 

We do not sell your personal information. We do not share it, except for the reasons described above. Therefore, there is no need for an opt-out process.

How do we use your medical information? We sometimes must collect medical information to provide you a product or to pay a claim. We do not use or share it, internally or externally, for any purpose except the following: 

  * underwriting insurance, 
  * administering your policy, account, or claim, 
  * as required or permitted by law, or 
  * as otherwise authorized by you. 

Questions?

We value our customers and want you to understand how we use the information we collect. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy.

We will provide you a copy of your personal information that we control and can reasonably retrieve. To access your information, you must provide the following: 

  1. All policy numbers you want to access. 
  2. Please sign your request and have your signature notarized. This ensures the identity of the person requesting the information. 
  3. We do not currently charge a fee to cover the cost of providing you with a copy of this information. However, we do reserve the right to charge a small fee in the future. 
  4. You may request that we correct your personal information in our files. Please note that we do not control information provided by third parties. So, you will need to contact the third party to correct any information from them. 
  5. Sometimes we obtain your consumer or credit report. If so, you may request the credit-reporting agency's name and address. You may ask the agency to give you a copy of your report. 

Please submit any inquiries to us at:  
Scottsdale Insurance Company  
Attn.: Compliance Manager  
P.O. Box 4110  
Scottsdale, Arizona 85261-4110

This privacy statement describes our privacy practices for both current and former customers. We will provide one copy of this notice to joint policy or contract holders; please share this information with everyone covered by your policy or contract. If you request, we will send more copies of this statement.

Thank you for choosing us.

We look forward to building a lifetime relationship with you.

DVM Insurance Agency  
Scottsdale Insurance Company  
National Casualty Company
